

RODRIGO **ALLENDE**

Summary

Hello! I am 37 years old, a marketer and a chef, venturing into web development to expand my skills and competencies. I am looking forward to getting my first job in the It sector either as a programmer or as a salesperson, for the moment finishing the odin project. My hobbies are traveling, learning, cooking and sports.

WORK EXPERIENCE

MANAGER

Distripack SAS (Comercial Management) June 2018 - June 2023

- Make purchases from our suppliers
- Take financial control of the company
- **Drive business decisions**

SALES REPRESENTATIVE

Prosegur (Sales) - Novembre 2017-June 2018-Madrid-España

- Sales management to add new clients to the Prosegur alarm
- Create new leads from different channels

CHEF DE PARTIE

Australia (Chef) August 2013-August 2017

- · Work as a team, following orders and having people in charge at the same time
- Work quickly meeting objectives, always maintaining quality and presentation standards
- Think and schedule tasks, plan weeks in advance.

ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE

L'ORÉAL (MARKETING Y PUBLICIDAD) October 2011 - June 2013-Cordoba-Argentina

- Training of personnel in sales techniques and development of business image
- Development of salons as a point of sale
- Control of customer service, downloading of guidelines to
- Organization of product launch events

BUSINESS ADVISOR

KADICARD CREDIT CARD - BANK - BANCO CREDICOOP (FINANCIAL SERVICE) March 2007 - July 2007 Cordoba-Argentina

- Queries and Claims
- Sales of financial products (Cards, loans and fixed terms)
 - Insurance sales

Contact information

OBISPO ORO STREET 461 4B NUEVA CÓRDOBA RODRIALLENDE86@GMAIL.COM TELÉFONO: 0351-152097461 HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/RODRIALLENDE

Academic training

ISPC INSTITUTO SUPERIOR POLITÉCNICO CÓRDOBA

Web programmer 2020-2020 Córdoba-Argentina

ILSC

Certificate IV International Trade 2016-2017 Brisbane-Australia

IES 21

MARKETING 2009-2013 Córdoba-Argentina

AZAFRAN

CHEF 2005-2007 Córdoba-Argentina

SKILLS

- English B2 Advance
- Creativity
- **Problem resolution**
- **Negotiation and Sales**
- Customer Relationship Management (CRM)
- **Decision capacity**
- Great Communication
- Efficient time management
- **Business** processes
- Business planning Web development
- HTML // CSS/ JAVASCRIPT
- Taking my first steps in React and Node JS